[ { "id": 0, 
    "question": "What is the difference (if any) between the \"input\" event and the \"change\" event?", 
	"correctAnswer": "d", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "They are essentially the same, but \"change\" is a proprietary event used in Internet Explorer."},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "The difference is that \"change\" only fires once when a field is modified the first time, while \"input \" fires each time input changes."},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "There is no difference and they can be used interchangeably."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "The \"change\" event occurs when input changes and the element then loses focus, while \"input\" occurs every time input is given."} ]
  },
  
 { "id": 1, 
    "question": "What is the result of defining a variable outside of any function?", 
	"correctAnswer": "b", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "The variable cannot be used in any functions."},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "It can be accessed by any script on the page."},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "Any code in the containing JavaScript file can access it."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "It will not be defined because it is not attached to any object."} ]
  },
  
 { "id": 2, 
    "question": "Why do we use closure in JavaScript? ", 
	"correctAnswer": "d", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "It reduces memory usage significantly."},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "It helps prevent errors."},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "It allows us to control access to variables and functions"},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "Both B and C"} ]
  },
  
 { "id": 3, 
    "question": "What is the best way to avoid dependency on load-order between different JavaScript files that are part of the same application?", 
	"correctAnswer": "a", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "Use a module which is imported into an immediately invoked function expression (IIFE) and return the modified module"},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "Download the JavaScript files from an external server."},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "Always make sure that the files are loaded in the correct order and include comments in the code with correct order."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "Put all JavaScript in a single file. "} ]
  },
  
  { "id": 4, 
    "question": "What is the purpose of the \"value\" attribute on HTML input elements?", 
	"correctAnswer": "d", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "It is used to uniquely identify the element within the DOM."},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "It can be used to access the value input by the user"},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "It can be used to store the value entered by the user and determine the initial value displayed."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "Both b and c are correct."} ]
  },
  
  { "id": 5, 
    "question": "When does the  \"blur\" event occur?", 
	"correctAnswer": "a", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter": "a", "value": "When the current input element is no longer selected"},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "When the input element is selected"},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "When the user scrolls down so that the input element is not longer visible"},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "When the page begins loading and a preloader blurs the screen."} ]
  },
  
  { "id": 6, 
    "question": "If global variable \"biz\" is defined as 1, what will happen if a function declares another variable with the same name and assigns a value of 2? ", 
	"correctAnswer": "d", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "An exception will be thrown since a variable with this name has already been defined."},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "The local variable will become an alias for the global variable, so any changes to it will change the global \"biz\" data. "},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "'1' will automatically be appended to the name of the local variable to mark it distinctly."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "The local variable will obscure the global \"biz\", so any changes to the local variable will not impact the global variable."} ]
  },
  
   { "id": 7, 
    "question": "When is an immediately invoked function expression (IIFE executed?)", 
	"correctAnswer": "a", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "When it is encountered by the JavaScript interpreter"},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "After the page has loaded."},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "It is not executed unless it is called explicitly"},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "None of the above are correct."} ]
  },
 
   { "id": 8, 
    "question": "What object is used as the container for global variables and functions within the page?", 
	"correctAnswer": "a", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "The window object"},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "The document object"},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "The navigator object"},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "The sessionStorage object"} ]
  },
  
  { "id": 9, 
    "question": "What does it mean when an input element gets focus?", 
	"correctAnswer": "d", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "The user enters input which modifies the content of the input element"},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "The user scrolls up or down such that the element is now visible."},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "The element has been loaded and is now displayed within the browser viewport."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "The user has selected the element so that it receives input."} ]
    }
   
]
				   